Hello friends, welcome to our YouTube channel.
Friends, today we will know about the
quarterly results of ICICI Prudential Life Insurance Company of this
Saffron series 21. I will go into the details of the result analysis of the quarterly
performance of ICICI Prudential Life Insurance Company.
Along with this,
we will discuss this thing.
Please do subscribe. If we
talk about the return of the company, then it is
46.33 percent return.
If we talk about the financial tank, then it is 11.92
percent return. If we talk about the market cap of the company, then it is
75 thousand 638 point 47
crore. Its share price has developed to
Rs. 724.30. The 52-week low was Rs. 434. The all-time
low is Rs. 226-paisa. The all-time low is Rs. 724, which is 30 percent at 724, which is the
all-time high. From our YouTube
channel's 52-week high, the
share price is trading at 532.55
paisa today. It is
trending at almost 26.4% discount. The
company's return on equity  8.7
vs
307 but only 5.27 PVC
phase if we talk about the company then 63.72
Industries pe 11.40 Industries pe the
recipe of this system is very industry wise from
but
subscribe that the company
comes from the insurance sector let's compare its affair
you can see the period of other staff also
you daddy Africa is 103 in such quality it is
told that 108 to such long and
quite to SBI Life Insurance has T3
rest like if we talk about general insurance
or New India their period is
completely low if we talk about return on
capital employed then you can see that
ICICI Prudential has 8.12 whereas
HDFC's computer subject
selection is long then if we
talk about ghee then you can see that
Kepler is almost let's talk about the quarter result, we
will analyze in detail
in our annual report if we look over and
here then there has been growth in sales in the
last quarter like Marg was 9930 this
quarter  Our operating profit has been 13003 crore. It
was 302 in the last quarter. In this quarter, it
went up to 698. If we
talk about gift tax, there is also a decline of
30 crores in it. Earlier, it is 315 crores now. If we
talk about net profit, then last
quarter it was 3 to 12 crores. This quarter our profit is
180 crores. That means there has been 40% growth and
our profit has also declined. If we
talk about earrings, our sales have
increased. Last year, our selective profit was 83
thousand 231 crores. This year,
our profit has declined from 62000 crores to 5 crores. That means our sales have
not grown. Our sales growth has decreased by 28.14% from last year.
If we look at the growth of operating profit
last year, we had
633 crores in operating and Sumit, this year the
operating profit was
1325 crores. That means our operating cost has increased
last year - 1.3%, this year - 2%.
If we talk about income, last year it
was 1099 crores and this year it is 2285 crores, due to which
we have made a net profit.
Profit revolt text last year
was 1219 crores and this year it is 961 crores. If we
talk about net profit, last year it
was 956 crores and this year it is 759 crores. Net profit
last year was 66665 and this year it is ₹5.28 paisa
because we had a net profit growth from last year.
That is why our
Ghaghra in
detail. Let us see further in the details.
Talking about the shareholding pattern,
in the promoters quota, ICICI Bank
Limited has 51.3%. Prudential Corporation
Holdings Limited has 22.09% and
SAIF has 16.35
%. Last quarter subscribed 4.2%. If we
talk about Republic, then it is 5.5%. In this way,
total promoters are
73.4%. Rest
six
subscribed.
In the next report, we will discuss each point in detail.
Now we come to point number two.
Point number  To have the recommendation of
final dividend of that point five, there
is very good news for the shareholders in the meeting of Equity Share Office Bureau to the member of companies which celebs headed for edge channel, that 55651 video
subscribe so that it is known in the channel meeting
that the company allotted shares to its employees under this scheme,
so this is
in point number-7, drink water in the
thirty first March 21 companies selected
90 equity share offer time, you should subscribe on this channel, if we
talk about the channel, then considered enough water
for you
can see that there has been improvement in the last quarter,
here
last
December
19 lakh 86 thousand 500 34 lakh our
subscription last
year was quite good
184 likes 8913 but this year our loss here has
reduced to 63 lakh 56 thousand 451,
if we talk about growth, then in this
4 percent growth our dividend has decreased that
If we talk about profit after tax, then
it has also decreased. Last
year it was 1,774.1 million rupees, this year it has
come down to 79,470 million rupees. If we talk about our profit after
tax, then that too has
decreased by approximately 6%.
If we talk about profit after tax, then that too has decreased by approximately
20.60 percent.
Today, we should see the growth of some operational metrics of the folder apps stake holders to see
what growth is happening. So let us
see the growth of 333 percent in the volume of new business.
This is a very good growth. If we talk about it, then there is a good growth in
that too. No
renewal
subscription is also
9106.
Subscribe to the
channel.
So subscribe here.
It is very good
under the management.
Some of the financial receivers of the company
which are given here, like acid
cover available, the company's growth is very
good here. Last year also it was 854 point 1408, this
year it is 855 percent. This is a slight improvement from last year.  The
debt-equity ratio is also
very good. Point 131st, this is a very
good recipe. If we talk about the debt service coverage ratio, it is
also good.
Last year it was 35.50 and this year it is
11.48. The
interest service coverage ratio is also good.
From 35.5 last year it is 11.48. If we talk about
standing redeemable preferences, there is
no ad warehousing here. Chapter
Leaders End: There is nothing here. If we
talk about the network, last year it
was 910994 and now it is 9 lakh 15 thousand 798.
It must be an improvement from last year
because the network has made profit and it has improved. The
net profit after tax last year
was 95602.16 and this year it is 75 thousand 922. If we
talk about shares on equity, we have already told
that there has been a minor decline from last year.
If we talk about current debt,
last year it was 104.5 percent and this
year it is 13.04 percent.  Percentage this current
ratio has decreased a bit
if we talk about long term debt working capital then
nothing has been given here bed to account receiver
here and have contributed if we talk like this then
last year it was 1.83 this year it is a little
bigger it has become 2.2 total dip total has been set if
we talk then last year it
was point six percent this year it is point five percent
this recipe and it smells very good the
greatest turnover festival all this is white in this
way some of their finalities are given here
if we talk about gas close then the
figure in lex here
is also positive in operating activities plus in minute and if we
look further then in net increase and decrease then
that is also in plus i.e. company is every
tier how is the permission to generate
generating capacity so overall
how did you like this video please tell us in the comment
thank you for watching this thank you